carouselchecks.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy of Carousel Checks

_Last updated August 5, 2013_

Protecting privacy is not new to Carousel Checks ("Carousel"). We have a long history of recognizing and protecting the privacy of consumers. Carousel is committed to protecting your privacy and utilizing technology that gives you the safest and most powerful online experience available. The following information will help you understand how Carousel collects, uses, and safeguards the information you provide through this Web site. Carousel Checks wants to assure you that when it asks for customer information, its goal is to improve customer relationships.

## Information Collection & Use

Carousel uses the information collected about you to process your order and to provide a better shopping experience. We may request that you voluntarily supply personal information for purposes such as receiving correspondence, registering on a Web site, making purchases, participating in online surveys or market research. If you elect to participate, Carousel may require personally identifiable information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, financial institution information, credit card information, or e-mail address. When you submit personal information to Carousel, you understand and agree that we may access, store, and use your information.

We may use your information to communicate with you about products, services, and future promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we offer you the option not to receive these types of communications. If you no longer wish to receive special offers or promotional notifications, please follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each communication. We may also send you order confirmation emails. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

Carousel does not rent or sell your personal information with third parties for them to market their products and services directly to you. We only share your personal information with companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order, billing processing, operational purposes, or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We reserve the right to disclose information about you:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, 
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, 
  * if Carousel is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

## Security

Carousel is committed to protecting your personal information. Security measures are in place on this Web site to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We offer industry-standard security measures available through your Web browser. When you are on this Web site, the sensitive information you provide such as credit card and financial information is encrypted with secure socket layer (SSL) technology and scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches us. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Please remember that e-mail, which is different from the encrypted sessions above, is not secure. Therefore, we ask that you do not send sensitive information such as credit card or account numbers to us via an unsecured e-mail message.

## Tracking Activity on our Web Site

In order to make your visit to our Web site as productive as possible, we track activity on our website. However, we want you to know that the tracking technology we use does not identify any personal information about you. It cannot retrieve data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture any personal information about you, such as your name, address, phone number, or email address. We only know who you are if you tell us.

As is true with most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically when individuals browse our site and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this non-personal information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole, in order to improve the functionality of the Web site. We use a third-party tracking service that uses technologies including clear gifs (e.g. web beacons) to track this non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate.

We use cookies to improve your shopping experience. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. A cookie may contain information (such as a unique user session ID) that is used to track the pages of the Web sites you've visited. The information in cookies helps to serve you better by keeping track of your order when shopping on this site; it also helps us improve site design. We may also use technologies such as cookies to provide you with enhanced online display advertising.  We do not store sensitive information, other than your name, in your cookies. 

We also contract with a third-party advertising partner to serve ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes on this site. They will collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partner, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices. Opting out will not in any way affect your use of our site.

Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can set your browser to decline cookies. Even if your Web browser is set to decline cookies, you can use many of the features within this site. However, you will not be able to place an order or retrieve your order status.

## Children Visiting our Web Sites

This Web site is directed at adults. We do not knowingly collect or use information from children. Should children access this Web site, we are confident that parents will not judge any of the information provided as objectionable for viewing. If you are under 18, you may use this Web site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

## Other Web Sites Linked to Carousels' Web Sites

Carousel is not responsible for the content or information practices employed by other Web sites that are linked to or from this Web site. In most cases, links to non-Carousel Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of this Web site.

## Our Commitment to the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act

Carousel maintains policies and procedures to help ensure that consumer data is used appropriately and within the scope of applicable laws. Information is made available for fraud prevention and detection purposes and for authorized criminal or government investigations. This information is made available in order to protect consumers and financial services companies; these disclosures are permitted by law. Carousel expresses our commitment to appropriate data use in our check-printing agreements with our financial institution customers.

## Consent to Privacy Policy/Changes to Privacy Policy

By using this Web site, you consent to our posted Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Web site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Your continued use of this Web site following the posting of changes to these terms means that you accept these changes.

We may change our privacy policy at any time. Any changes to the privacy and security policy will be posted on this Web site so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, as well as the latest updates on how we maintain the secure portions of our Web site. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the changes becoming effective.

Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the confidentiality of information. These reviews are conducted by internal staff who report directly to the Carousel Board of Directors, external auditing and accounting firms, and government regulators. Included in these self-assessments and examinations are reviews of the controls and safeguards related to consumer privacy described in our Privacy Policy.

## To Correct/Update/Access/Opt Out/Deactivate:

Carousel is committed to ensuring that the information we obtain and use is accurate. Please use the contact information below to ask questions or review, update or correct the personally identifiable information that was collected online from you. If you no longer wish to receive special offers or promotional communications, please follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each communication. Our service representatives are trained to answer questions about and give you reasonable access to your personal information in our database.

## Contacting Carousel

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Web site or your dealings with this Web site, Carousel provides the following convenient ways to contact us:

Carousel Checks  
11152 Southwest Hwy.  
Palos Hills, IL 60465

Carousel Checks is a BBB accredited business and complies with BBB Online standards.
